Now it's time to set sail!
Oh, here it comes. Here it comes.
What?
I've never seen anything like it.
Looks like a deep-sea fish.
Wow!
Hello everyone! I'm Mirei Sasaki from Hyugaizaka 46.
Ta-da!
Today we're at the sea. Wow! This is Odawara fishing port.
The reason why we're here is because today we're going to be
Sea Fishing Loose Meepan Channel
I like fishing, and I usually go fishing from time to time.
I like fishing and sometimes I go fishing, but today I'm here for sea fishing.
Today...
There's a friend of mine over there.
Hey, mate.
My friends!
We are friends.
Yay!
I'm Tayaka Fukuyama.
I'm Tayaka Fukuyama
Yay!
I've been following Lipan's fishing
Yes, Aya bought a knife last time
I bought it
For cutting fish
She bought it.
Yes, so I want Aya to cook it for me.
Yay!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm going to cook!
By the way, it's 4:30 in the morning.
I'm serious.
I didn't sleep today.
I didn't sleep.
Today, my goal is to catch a red snapper.Today, my goal seems to be to catch a red snapper.
I like ama-nai.
It's fun. I think it's a fish that lives in the deep.
I see.
I'll have to give it a try.
I'll give it a try.
Let's set sail!
We're moving forward.
The pirate cage. We're in it.
It's moving. It's boffoing.
I'm really excited. I'm really happy.
Oh, look, the sun's out.
It's bright. I'm so happy.
It's nice, but it's kind of nasty.
It's not the glare of the summer heat. It's still morning.
No, that's right. Not yet.
I'm wearing long sleeves.
I'm wearing long sleeves. - Oh, yeah, the fishing room. It's so cute.
I'm orange. I'm lacra.
Yay! Yay!
It's very stylish for everyday use.
Very stylish. Cute.
Looks like boots. Oh, boots.
Boots. Cute.
This is what a girlfriend looks like.
From a boyfriend's point of view. From a girlfriend's point of view?
Men are so dazzling...
Dazzling.
Hey, catch a lot of fish.
Catch a lot of fish.
It's fun
Let's see how cool you are.
That's funny.
What's this?
I'll do it.I'll do this.
I'll do this.
I'll do this, I'll do that, I'll do that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey...
Oh, no. Today was Mee Bread Day.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It looks like it's about to start.
Okay, I'm off to the sea.
You there? You know, I was thinking...
But I feel like even if there were little ones, they'd still be little.
Wow! Oh, my gosh! There it is!
Oh, this way.
I got a fish!
It's so tiny!
That's great! I caught it!
What kind of fish is this?
It's a bigeye snapper.
A rock porgy? That's amazing! It's a snapper, but...
It's not a tie, but it's a tie.
No way! I've never caught one before.
It's fun! It's fun when you know you caught it.
I don't know about that.
Is it there?
No, I don't.
I don't know.
Maybe it's not here.
I think I'll just fry it up.
It's so heavy.
It's really heavy.
It's heavy.
There's some fish in there!
There's more fish.
What's that? Is it alive?What's that? Is he alive?
Is he?
You're here?
He's so cute.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy.
You're alive.
It's alive.
When did you eat it?
Wow, my eyes moved.
My eyes moved.
Wow, that's great.
Mr. Big Ham!
No, I just thought I'd fry it up once anyway.
I'll replace the shrimp.
Oh, there's something in there! Again!
A small one.
Fitness.
Aah! Here it comes!
I made a mistake. I made a mistake.
Something's coming.
What?
It's not much.
Oh, I think it's coming! I'm getting a buzz!
I think there's something in here!
No way!
I think I'm getting a buzz!
Oh, there it is!
Oh, my God!
What is it? A camera!
Wind?
What is that?
I'm scared.
You're looking at it.
You're scaring me.I'm scared!
Hang in there.
This girl is breathing so well.
It's fun.
Fishing is fun even when you're not thinking about it.
Catching a big one.
It's fun to catch two big ones.
I knew it!
Two, two, two pangs, three fish.
It's so much fun. It's my dream.
I've been saying I wanted to fish ever since I became an idol.
But I've been taking chances and fishing all the time, so I'm really happy to be able to do this.
I'm so happy to be able to go on Youtube!
I want to fish for tuna and salmon too!
So I still have a lot of things to do.
I want to go back to Japan!
So I'm going back to Japan for the first time!
It's so heavy!
There's this one! It's really crooked!
There's something here!
What is that?
Scary.
I've never seen anything like it.
Looks like a bullet train.
What is it?
It's an attache.
A bite?
We got reds!
That's a big one. I've never seen this fish before.
Oh, my God.
Amadayizu, I hope I don't lose you.
I was just singing, and there it was.
Oh, there it is again.
That's a tough one.
Oh, no...
There's something in there.There's something there.
But I don't think there's that many.
It's early.
Oh, there's something here.
Wait a minute.
It's a princess. A princess.
Here's something.
I hope you get to meet her while she's still alive.
Oh, my God.
What's that?
It's tiny.
Tiny.
Oh, my God.
Yellow pattern.
I wonder if there's something in there.
I don't see anything.
Oh, uh, hmm?
Maybe there's something in there.
Oh, there it is.
We got a hit.
What are you doing?
I got the same thing.
It's the same one as the heel-in-pants one.
He's breathing very well.
It's true.
But I can't take her now, she's dead.
I can't get her.
Avatar.
What is it?
I thought I heard voices.
I think it's above ground.
How many aba-dai did you catch?
One?
Oh, two.
Two... two little ones together.
I'm starting to lose track.I'm starting to lose my senses.
I want a miracle
I don't think there's anything out there.
I hope one of us catches it.
I don't see anything.
Well, there you are, Meeper.
-Oh, my God, not again. That's him. That's him?
You're my friend.
I'm glad. I'm glad. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Your friend.
Your friend caught it. I thought it was a sea bream.
Ahhh!
LOL!
I don't want to do tuning clothes
I'll hurry up and put it in.
LOL!
I fished for about 2 hours.
I didn't get a big one.
Grass
It's so hard!
But it's fun to fish.
I can be mindless!
So I came back.
I'm back!
It's so bright!
It's morning
So now
Let's start processing
Let's start processing.
Yay!
First, the fish.
I'll open it.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Open.
Ta-da!
There are fish.
Like this.
A big hole in the table.
The one Aya caught.
Shall we cut them up?
Janko's
Mai Gut
Yes, sir.
Let's take it out.
Wow!
I bought this the other day.
Here, ayaka.
Hmm? Here.
That's it.
The one I asked you to hold.
Right there.
I'll handle it right then and there.
Yes, please.
First, remove the scales.
I'm removing the scales.
Yes, sir.
Is it removed?
Yeah, it looks good.
No, it doesn't look good.
First, I'll remove the head.
I'll drop the head.
Looks firm.
Wow, the bones are great. They're really solid.
That's the important thing.
Three pieces?
Three.
That's good.That's good.
There it is.
It looks a little better.
All right, here it comes. Sashimi.
Other side.
Oh, there's a little meat...
Oh, here...
Careful.
Oh, here it comes!
Here it comes!
Wow!
Three.
Did you have fun?
I was able to unload 3 cards!
Yay!
Was it difficult?
But I think Thailand is easy to get up.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I can't do it.
Oh!
Oh, I got it!
From?
I'm getting a little burnt on this one.
The skin?
Yes.
I'm going to sear this. The skin.
I hear it looks good.
We will cut it.
Finished.
Wow! Thank you very much.
Aya is a knife with a knife.
This was a burn.
She used a knife to cut the fish,
The fish you just caught, sashimi and seared? She made seared sashimi.That fish you just caught, sashimi and seared? He made it into seared sashimi.
Well then.
Well then. Let's eat.
Let's eat.
Enjoy.
Sashimi.
Looks puripuri.
Bon appétit. Here we go.
Ready.
Mmm.
How is it?
Very soft and juicy.
It's good.
Tasty?
How about seared?
You like it seared?
Of course.
Bon appétit.
I wonder what the difference is.
Mmm!
Is it good?
Yes, it is.
Delicious!
The aroma is different!
If you can eat it.
Yes.
Delicious!
Try it, Aya.
Want some?
Crunchy!
Bon appétit.
Yes!Yes!
I know, right?
It's so plump!
I wonder if it's because they're freshly harvested.
It's amazing!
Delicious!
I seared the skin.
Yum, yum, yum.
Bon appétit!
It's delicious.
It's so juicy, isn't it?
Fresh off the vine!
Oh, my God, it's fresh.
Delicious!
It's amazing how fresh it is.
The texture is so different.
It's amazing.
I don't think Thai fish is that crispy.
It's totally different.
Delicious!
It's so good!
My ultimate goal is...
I dream of catching a tuna
I dream of holding a tuna fishing event
I'm counting on you!
Let's make it happen together!
Thank you for watching
Thank you very much.
Good button and subscribe to our channel
Thank you for your comment!
Bye bye!
Nieper's itch.
Is that what you wanted to do?
Yes, that's what I wanted.
You've been following me.You're following me.
There you go.
That was fun.
It was fun.
That was frustrating.
So frustrating.
I didn't catch any ama-edai.
I didn't catch the ama-edai, but...
I hope I caught your heart.
Grass.
You thought it was grass when you said it.
She's lovely.
Thank you.
She was wonderful.
Yay.
[ED]